A Finding Aid to the Yasuo Kuniyoshi Papers, 1906-2013, in the Archives of American Art AAA.kuniyasu
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1920s-2001; Series 6; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 3, 9, 15; (Box 3; 1 folder)
  - Oversize Photographs of Kuniyoshi at Whitney Museum Dinner from Box 9, Folder 12, 1948 (Box 15)
  - Oversize Photographs of Kuniyoshi with Others from Box 9, Folder 13, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 15)
  - Oversize Photographs of Sara Mazo Kuniyoshi from Box 9, Folder 17, circa 1940s (Box 15)
  - Oversize Exhibition Installation Photographs from Box 9, Folder 23, circa 1940s (Box 15)
- Artwork, 1927-circa 1940s; Series 7; 0.2 Linear feet Boxes 3, 9, OV 4
  Artwork includes numerous pencil sketches by unidentified artists, two zinc lithographic plates made by Kuniyoshi, and two lithographs printed from the plates. Also found are Christmas cards designed by Kuniyoshi.
  - Sketches by Unidentified Artists, undated (Box 3 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Zinc Lithographic Plates, 1927; (Oversized material housed in OV 4) (Box 3 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Lithographs, 1927; (Oversized material housed in OV 4) (Box 3 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Christmas Cards by Kuniyoshi, circa 1940s (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Oversized Zinc Lithographic Plates, (See Box 3, F7) (Box OV 4)
  - Oversized Lithographs, (See Box 3, F8) (Box OV 4)
- Exhibition Files, 1953-2004; Series 8; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 9-10
  Exhibition files were created by Sara Mazo Kuniyoshi and only include exhibitions of Kuniyoshi's works after his death in 1953. Files may include exhibition checklists and planning documents, loan agreements, correspondence, photographs of the exhibition, and press materials.
  Files are arranged chronologically by year of exhibition. Researchers should note that additional exhibition records may be found within Series 4: Subject Files.
  - "Ink Paintings," Downtown Gallery (1953) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - "Circus Themes," Downtown Gallery (1955) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kuniyoshi Memorial Exhibition, Woodstock Art Gallery (1956) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Retrospective Exhibition, Boston University (1961), 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "Drawings & Lithographs," Downtown Gallery (1965), 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - "Kuniyoshi," Nihonbashi Gallery (1965) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Retrospective Exhibition, University of Florida (1969), 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 36-37)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi: Drawings and Graphics," F.A.R. Gallery (1970), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi: A Retrospective Exhibition," University of Texas (1975), 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 39-41)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi," Chrysler Museum at Norfolk (1978) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - "Drawings, 1918-1924," Ellen Sragow Gallery (1979) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi: Drawings of the Forties," Zabriskie Gallery (1980) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Drawings Exhibition, Japan (1980-1981) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi: Artist as Photographer," Norton Gallery/Bard College (1983), 1982-1990 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
  - "Drawings of the 1920s," Zabriskie Gallery (1986) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi," Whitney Museum of American Art, Philip Morris (1986-1987), 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Yasuo Kuniyoshi Retrospective, Nippon Television Network (1989), 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Retrospective Exhibition, National Museum of Modern Art, Kyoto (1989) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - "Yasuo Kuniyoshi: Drawings from the 1930s-1940s," Louis Newman Galleries (1991) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - "Female Nudes: Drawings of the 1930s and 1940s," Zabriskie Gallery (1991) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Exhibition at Meguro Museum of Art, Tokyo (1992-1993) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - "The Shores of A Dream," Amon Carter Museum (1997), 1991-2001 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - "Six American Painters and the Photograph," Zabriskie Gallery (2001) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Kuniyoshi: A Retrospective," National Museum of Modern Art, Tokyo (2004), 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Artwork Records, circa 1920s-2004; Series 9; 3.3 Linear feet Boxes 10-13, 16, 18
  Artwork records were created by Sara Mazo Kuniyoshi to document works of art created by her husband. Files mostly include photographs of artwork with annotations regarding title, date, sale, and provenance. Some files also include correspondence regarding the exhibition, sale, or authentication of specific works of art, notes by Sara Kuniyoshi, exhibition history, and published reproductions.
  Files are arranged based on Sara Mazo Kuniyoshi's original order. Glass plate negatives which were found within the files were separated into preservation storage containers and are closed to researchers.
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, A-B, circa 1940s-2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, C-D, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, E-G, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, H-M, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, P-S, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Casein and Gouache Paintings, T-Y, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Drawings, A-B, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Drawings, C-E, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Drawings, F-G, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Drawings, H-L, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Drawings, M-Q, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Drawings, S, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Drawings, T-Y, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Drawings Authenticated, 1974-2001 (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
  - Drawings, Miscellaneous, circa 1979-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
  - Ink Drawings, circa 1960s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Ink Drawings, Miscellaneous, 1970s-1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lithographs, circa 1982-1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lithographs (Photographs only), circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lithographs Checklist, 1950-1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Paintings, Individual Files (Box 10)
    - Abandoned Treasures (1946), circa 1946-1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Accordion and Horse (1938), circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Acrobats (1925), circa 1950s-1976 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Alabaster Vase and Fruit (1928), circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - All Alone (1938), circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Al Perkins Drying Fish (1922), circa 1920s-1950s (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Amazing Juggler (1952), circa 1950s-1960s; 1990s (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Artificial Flower and Other Things (1934), circa 1950s; 1980s (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Autumn Twilight (1929), circa 1920s; 1970 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - The Baby (1921), circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Baby Frightened by Water (1925), undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Bachelor's Child, 2001; circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Bananas and Plums (circa 1926), circa 1991 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Bathers (before 1920), circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Bather Under Water (1924), circa 1920s (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Bather with Cigarette (1924), circa 1962; 1993 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Bathing Beauty (1924), 1979-1980; circa 1920s (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Bessie (1941), 1990s; circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Between Two Worlds (1939), circa 1940-1960s (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Big Round Table with Objects (1927), circa 1920s (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Bouquet on Stove (1929), circa 1920s-1997 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Boy Feeding Chickens (1923), 1997; 2001 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Boy Fishing (1921), circa 1968 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Boy Frightened by Snake (1921), 1920s-1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Boy Stealing Fruit (1923), circa 1920s-2000 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Boy Taking Cow Home (1921), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Broken Objects (1944), 1940s-1995 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Burgundy (1935), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - By The Sea (1943), circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Cafe (1937), 1990; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Captain's Daughter (1924), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Carnival (1948-1949), 1950s (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Chicken Yard (1921), circa 1950s; 1970s (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Child (1923), circa 1950s; 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Child (1947-1948), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Circus Ball Rider (1930), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Circus Girl (1931), circa 1930s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Circus Girl Resting (1925), circa 1920s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The Cock Calling the Dawn (1923), 1920s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Cow, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cow and Girl (circa 1948-1949), 1989-1990s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Cows in Pasture (1923), 1920s-1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Cripple Creek (1941), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Crucifixion, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Daily News (1935), 1940s-1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Dawn is Coming (1944), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Day of Rest (1925), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Deliverance (1947), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Deserted Brick Yard (1938), circa 1940s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Doughnuts and Grapes (1932), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Dream (1922), circa 1940s; 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Dream Girl (1946-1948), circa 1940s; 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Eggplant (1925), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Empty Town in Desert (1943), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - End of Juanita (1942), circa 1950s; 1993 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Eve in the Garden of Eden (1946), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Exit (1948-1950), 1950-1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Fakir (1951), 1950s-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Farmyard, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Festivities Ended (1939-1947), circa 1950s-1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Fish and Seaweed (circa 1921), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fisherman's Son (1922), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Fish Kite (1950), circa 1950-1980s (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Flapper (1921), circa 1920s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Flowers (1925), circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Flowers (1926), 1987; circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Flowers (1932), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Flowers in Vase (1930), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Forbidden Fruit (1950), 1998; 1960s (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - A Friend (1945), circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Friends (1948), circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - From Pine Hill (1920), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Fruit on Stove (1930), circa 1930s (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Fruit, Reproduction and Cookies (1934), circa 1950s-1998 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Fruits on Table (1931), circa 1960 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Girl Asleep, circa 1950s-1997 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Girl at Piano (1921), circa 1920s; 1980s (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Girl at Table (1920), undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Girl Brushing Hair (1928), circa 1930s (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Girl Combing Hair (1928), circa 1930s (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Girl in Armchair, 1981-2001 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Girl in Chemise on Sofa (1925), circa 1920s; 1987 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Girl in Gray Chemise (1929), circa 1920s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Girl in Green (1933), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Girl in Pink Slip (1932), 1988; 1998 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Girl in Red Skirt, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Girl in White (1934), circa 1950s-2001 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Girl in White Chemise (1928), 1950s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Girl in Wicker Chair (1929), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Girl Reading (1927), circa 1988 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Girl Thinking (1935), 1960s-1998 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Girl Wearing Bandana (1936), circa 1987-1997 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Girl with Accordion (1941), circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Girl with Ball (1922), circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Girl with Bangs, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Girl with Cigarette, 1989; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Girl with Feathered Hat (1935), circa 1950s; 1989 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Girl with Flowered Hat (1929), 1991-1992; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Girl with Flower in Hair (1932), circa 1932 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Girl with Fur Coat (1930), 1988; circa 1951 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Girl with Handkerchief, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Girl with Hat (1924), circa 1978 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Going Out (1934), 1999; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Good Little Girl (1921), 1920s (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Grapes and Hard Crackers (1935), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Grapes on a Kerchief, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Grapes, Peanut Brittle and Peaches, circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Grapes, Pipe, and Other Things (1935), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Headless Horse Who Wants to Jump (1945), 1946-1989 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Head of a Young Girl (1934), circa 1930s (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Honeycomb Hill (1941), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - House in Landscape, 1989; 1999 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - I Like It Here (1944), circa 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - I'm Tired (1938), 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Interior with Still Life (1927), circa 1920s-1974 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Island of Happiness (1924), 1920s; 1994 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - I Think So (1938), 1930s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - I Was Just Married (1939), 1950s; 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - I Wear Mask Today (1946), circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Joel's Barn (1923), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Joinville (1925), 1988; circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Just A Nice Day (1946-1947), 1996; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Landscape (1918), circa 1991 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Landscape (early 1920s), circa 1973 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Landscape (1920s), 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Landscape (1924), 1950s; 1937 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Landscape (1925), 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Landscape with Donkey (1928), 1950s-1978 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Landscape with Two Dogs (1945), 1981; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Lay Figure (1937-1938), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Life Saver (1925), circa 1920s; 1977 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Little Joe with Cow (1923), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Little Pond (1932), circa 1945 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Look, It Flies! (1946), 1940s-1975 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Lover's Pike (1946), circa 1950s; 1984 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Maine Family (1923), 1999; 1990; 1963 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Maine Landscape (1923), 2001; circa 1974 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Maine Landscape (circa 1924), circa 1920s-1986 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Maud (1921), 1979; circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - The Meeting (1921-1922), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Melon, Grapes and Pears (1929), 1950s-1985 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Milking Cow (1921), circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Milk Maid (1924), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Milk Train (1940), circa 1950s; 1989 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Mirror (1933), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Mr. Ace (1952), 1990; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Model Walking Around Studio (1924), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Morning After (1938), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Mother and Daughter (1945), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - My Fate is in Your Hand (1950), 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Nevadaville (1942), circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Nude (Multiple) (Early), 1990; 1994 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Nude (1929), circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Nude at Stairway, circa 1976 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Nude Dressing at Window, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Nude on Couch (1922), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Nurse and Child (1924), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Odd Objects on Couch (1929-1930), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Ogunquit Landscape (1923), undated (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Oriental Presents (1951), 1950s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Painting on Mirror, undated (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Paula in Green (1940), circa 1950s; 1985 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Peaches and Grapes (1929), circa 1950s; 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Photograph and Peaches on Chair (1938), 1970; circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Picking a Horse (1937), circa 1930s-1997 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Picnic, circa 1978 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Pigeon and Scarf (1932), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Poppies (1928), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Portrait of a Young Girl (1933), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Portrait of a Young Girl (1933), circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Praying for Rain (circa 1923), circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Quiet Thought, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Reclining Nude (1929), circa 1950s; 1989 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Refugees (1917), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Relaxation (1942), circa 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Resting (circa 1920), circa 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Resting (1930), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Revelation (1948-1949), 1950s (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Rolls (1931), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Rolls on Chair (1930), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Room 110 (1944), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Rotting on the Shore (1945), circa 1950s; 1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Season's Ended (1940-1945), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Seated Girl, 1968; 1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Seated Nude (1920), undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Self-Portrait (1918), circa 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Self-Portrait (1924), 1950s-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Self-Portrait as a Golfer (1927), 1950s-1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - She's Going (1944), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - She Walks Among the Ruins (1945-1946), 1949-1970s (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Sisters Frightened by Whale (1923), 1920s-1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Skating (1931), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Sleeping Girl (1928), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Somebody Tore My Poster, 1949-1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Spanish Soprano (1942), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Standing Nude (circa 1939-1941), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Still life (1928), circa 1950s; 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Still Life with Bananas (1920), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Still Life with Fruit, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Stormy Weather (1936), circa 1950s; 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Strong Woman and Child (1925), circa 1950s-2000 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Sugar Doll (1929), circa 1950s; 1980s (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Summer (1929), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Summer Storm (1938), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Susanna (1944), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Swimmer (1924), 1999; circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Things on Iron Chair (1936), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Thinking Ahead (1945), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - This Is My Playground (1947), 1948-1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Three Generations (1920), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Three Peaches (1938), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - La Toilette (1927), circa 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - To The Ball (1950), 1950-2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Toward Village (1937), circa 1950s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Toy Tiger and Odd Objects (1932), circa 1950s-1988 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Trapeze Performer (1940), circa 1940s (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Try-on (1942), 1989; circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Twisted Bread (1930), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Two Babies (1923), circa 1920s (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Two Cows (1922), circa 1950s-1986 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Two Sisters (1920), circa 1920s (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Upside Down Table and Mask (1940), 1941-1992 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Upstream (1922), 1920s-2000 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Village (1921), circa 1950s; 2003 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - White Cow in Marsh (1921), circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Wild Horses (1921), circa 1920s; 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Winter Landscape (1921), circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Woman and Child (1920), circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Woman in Flat (1920), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Yellow Flowers (1919), circa 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Young Couple (1923), circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Young Girl, 1982; circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Your Fate Is In My Hand (1950), circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Waiting (1938), circa 1940s (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Waitresses (1924-1925), circa 1950s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Watermelon (1938), circa 1950s; 1990s (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Weathervane and Other Objects, circa 1950s; 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - What's the Use (1940), circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Photographs of Artwork, Miscellaneous, circa 1940s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
    Oversized items housed in Box 16
  - Reproductions of Artwork "Not in Files", circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Oversize Photographs of Artwork from Box 13, Folder 16, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 16)
  - Glass Plate Negatives of Photographs of Artwork, circa 1930s (Box 18)
- Scrapbooks, 1919-1978; Series 10; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 13-14, 17
  Four scrapbooks include press clippings, exhibition announcements, checklists, and a few catalogs. Three of the scrapbooks appear to have been compiled in chronological order from 1919 to 1951. The fourth scrapbook appears to have been created at a later date by Sara Mazo Kuniyoshi.
  - Scrapbook, circa 1933-1978 (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
  - Scrapbook, 1919-1931 (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Scrapbook, 1934-1945 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1946-1951 (Box 17, Folder 2)